

: motsebo@gmail.com

**(2)** 

: 309-532-7479



: https://patkloe.github.io/portfolio/

:

https://patkloe.github.io/

Memphis, TN 38119

## **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

## **Summary:**

I am a full stack developer with a 360-degree view on product development process. I am focused on web quality, keep learning more software languages, client and server sides to develop products for customer satisfaction.

- Always, high motivated, self-learner, people person.
- · Having worked with some corporate for their website developments. Developed websites such as

Websites	<b>Technology</b> Dates
http://www.patcindy-biz.com	Mvc, aspx, Html5, May 2016 Css3, JQuery
http://www.georgiagames.org/	Css3, Html5, Dhtml, Mar 2010 - Aug Xhtml, Xml, Flash, ActionScript, JQuery, Json, JavaScript,, S.E.O
http://www.ubia.fr/	Css2, ASP, Flash, ActionScript, PHP4, Dhtml, Html4, Sql, S.E.O, JavaScript

http://touchofgodministries.org/en/overv iew/	Joomla, Jreview,Html, Php, JavaScript	Jan 2008 – Mar 2008
http://www.gospel- river.com/fr/Accueilhttp://www.gospelriver.com/fr/AccueilGospel-	Asp, html4, Css2,C# Photoshop,	Sep 2006 – Oct 2007
River.htmGospelRiver.htm	JavaScript	
https://www.jeremiesion.com/fr/	Css, PHP4, Dhtml, Html, Sql,Javascript, Json, S.E.O, Joomla 1.5, Drupal 5	Jun 2003 – Dec 2007

- Over 5 years of experience in Developing video, Scripts with Flash ActionScript and Java Script for the ecommerce website
- Have expertise over Search Engine Optimization.
- Developed in school: some applications with Java, PL/SQL
- Change theme with Drupal(Drupal theming), Add modules, manage users

### Skills:

Operating Systems: Windows 2003/2008 Server, Windows 2000, XP, Vista, 7, 10, Linux Redhat, Mandrake.

Web server: Apache, IIS

Internet/Network Protocol: Http, TCP/IP, Ftp, Dhcp, Dns. Comet, isp

Systems: Linux (mandrake, Redhat, Fedora), Windows (Xp, Vista, Nt, 7, advance server, 2003), Macos CMS: Joomla,

Dotnetnuke.

Languages: Python, Php, Java, C, C# "learning" Web:

Html5/CSS3/ JavaScript.

Relational databases: Dbase, MySQL, Oracle, Access, SQLite

PHP/ (JavaScript and Html) Framework: Windows framework 4.0, Laravel, Bootstrap4, Font Awesome Best

**Practices:** SEO (Search Engine Optimization)

Development Methodology, Tools agile, Git, GitHub

Other: Camtasia, filemaker, office 2007, xp, Git, Putty, Winscp, skills on section 508, Power BI, Microsoft Data Azure Hardware: motherboard, power supply, (sound, graphic, video, network 'lan'/'wan'/'Wi-Fi') cards, memory (sdram, dimm), Hdd (Ide, sata)

## **Professional Experiences:**

## Currently

Software Developer Engineer "Freelance"

For some customers remote works on their websites using Drupal, Joomla. Html, Css, JavaScript, Mysql, Php.

Depending of the Customer needs. Migrating applications PHP-PYTHON, Updates some files, load those files to their servers through FileZilla, Winscp, GitHub

## JABIL INC Circuit, Memphis, TN

Mar 2011 - July 2019

Web developer

Responsibilities:

Develop web pages to drive Test process.

Using JavaScript, Html5, Css3, MySQL, Sql, Php

They assemble servers' data storage, and then they will give a life to those servers through customers test software.

Built a database using MySQL, to interact with the database tables, I used language side server PHP.

Retrieve some data on the database, generated some reports, and presented them under some pie charts to help for analysis and statistics.

# Statefarm insurance, Bloomington, IL

Sept 2010 - Feb 2011

Web analyst

Responsibilities:

- Developed an intranet named "Dashboard" where they are able to get their nationwide system status; I used Html5, Css3, Xml, and JavaScript.
- Analyzed some 'csv' files, create tables in MYSQL database, I was using Sass Enterprise Guide for reporting, generated and updated some html files where the result is presented through some charts.
- Generated, provided some flash files using Xcelsius for the application 'Dashboard'

Georgia games, Kennesaw, GA

Sept 2009 - Aug 2010 Senior/Web Application Developer

Responsibilities:

http://georgiagames.org/index.html Updated the current Website

Sometimes, worked at home, using ftp application to download and upload the file on the server, using Html, Dhtml, JavaScript, Xml, and Xhtml.

Cm2s, France, Paris

June 2009 - Aug 2009 Senior/Web Application

Developer

### Responsibilities:

Coordinated change control procedures with existing support and management groups

Served as a Liaison with programmers & engineers resolving technical problems with business applications and hardware configurations

- Developed websites with content management system: joomla, jreview and Drupal. MySQL
- Developed some websites using Html, Dhtml, JavaScript, ActionScript, Xml, Xhtml, Css, S.E.O

### THELLIGENCE INTERNATIONAL FRANCE

Nov 2008 - May 2009 Web

### **Application Developer Responsibilities:**

- Developed Web application using **MVC** technology to assist customers.
- Created Videos with Flash, created Banners, Images with Photoshop, Illustrator.
- Worked with File Transfer Protocol (FTP) to load files on server
- Managed web domain of customer mail accounts and database administration accounts
- Created graphics design on websites to advertise clients information
- Worked on threaded discussion group access and displayed in a variety of formats using PHP/MySQL, Css,
   JQuery and JavaScript (both client-side and server-side), S.E.O
- Developed video, 3D Scripts with Flash, ActionScript for the Customers Websites
- Developed and maintained some websites, using Html, Dhtml, JavaScript, Dreamweaver, Flash, Photoshop, Illustrator

### **Education:**

Currently taking programming class at Tech901 – Memphis. TN

- Master Degree in Computer Science at Orsay's Faculty of Sciences-France
- Bachelor of Science, Computer science at Luminy faculty of sciences-France 
   <sup>(1)</sup> "HTML5/CSS3" intermediate certificate from Kennesaw state University.
- JavaScript Certificate from W3schools.com
- Currently code 1.0 at Tech901 Memphis, TN
- Training on Power BI/Microsoft Data Azure